(Penny:)Come on, I think I have decaf.
(Sheldon:)Oh, good, Stuart.
I thought I heard your voice.
(Sheldon:)- Do you have a moment?
- Uh, yeah, I guess.
(Penny:)We're a little busy here, so...
- What are you doing?
- We're having coffee.
(Sheldon:)Isn't it a little late for coffee?
(Stuart:)It's okay. She thinks she has decaf.
(Penny:)I'll just go look for it.
- What's up?
- Well, I've spent the last three hours...
...in a debate in the DC Comics Batman
chat room, and I need your help.
(Stuart:)Oh, yeah. Those guys can be
very stubborn. What's the topic?
(Sheldon:)I am asserting in the event
that Batman's death proves permanent...
...the original Robin, Dick Grayson,
is the logical successor to the Bat Cowl.
(Stuart:)Ooh, Sheldon, I'm afraid
you couldn't be more wrong.
"More wrong"?
(Sheldon:)Wrong is an absolute state
and not subject to gradation.